Hello.
こんにちは
Thank you for today.
今日はありがとうございます
Re-dye your hair.
髪染め直して
I've been dyeing it.
染めてきた
Feels good.
いい感じ
What color did you use before?
前は何色やった?
Blonde?
金髪?
Since it's a video, I think it looks good.
動画なんだからね、似合うと思う
Is today a day off?
今日は休みですか?
I have a day off today.
今日は休みです
You came on your day off today, what do you usually do with your time?
今日は休みに来てくれたけど、普段は何して過ごすことが多い?
Sleeping or playing with the cat.
寝てるか、猫と遊んでる
Don't you have a cat?
猫飼ってないの?
How many?
何匹?
Do cats need care?
猫ってお世話はいる?
Almost unnecessary.
ほぼいらない
What about bait?
餌は?
Just give it twice.
2回あげるだけ
Isn't it okay when I get home?
家帰ったらおらへんとかない?
Looks like it'll come out somewhere.
どっかで出るみたいな
I'm at home, but no one will come to pick me up.
一応家の中にいるけど、お迎えは来ない
I miss you.
寂しいね
Don't they go somewhere on their own, like Sazae-san's balls?
サザエさんの玉みたいにさ、勝手にどっか行ってるとかない?
When Tsusu is missing but you can't find him at home.
つすがいないけど、家の中で探せないときは
It's spacious.
広いですね
Like the person at the washing machine.
洗濯機の人とかに
Cats can fit in there, right?
猫ってなんか、そこ入れるんやっていうようなとこ入るよね
Is it thin?
細いんかな?
That's right.
そ っかそっか
Are you more of a cat person than a dog person?
犬より猫派か
There are also dogs.
犬もいます
Don't you fight?
喧嘩しない?
We're good friends.
仲いいね
Maybe it's because we live together.
一緒に住んでるからかな
That's amazing.
すごいね
Both?
両方か
Will the dog be like woof when you get home?
犬は帰ったらワンワンみたいな?
The dog hasn't come either.
犬も来ない
Isn't there enough love?
愛情足りてないじゃないですか?
Like someone who gives food.
ご飯あげる人みたいな
That's right.
そうなんや
I still don't know much about dogs, compared to cats.
まだ犬はなんかね、猫と比べると
I guess you could say it's a bit friendly.
ちょっと人懐っこいというかね
That's right.
そうなんや
I miss you.
寂しいね
So, on my days off, I usually do indoors.
じゃあ休みの日も基本インドアみたいな
It's hot and lonely.
暑いし寂しい
Don't you have any hobbies?
趣味とかもないの?
hobby?
趣味?
cooked rice?
ご飯?
cooking?
料理?
Or go out to eat.
食べに行くとか
Do you also like cooking?
料理も好き?
I also like cooking.
料理も好き
It's okay to cook by yourself.
自炊じゃあいいよ
Properly.
ちゃんと
What is your specialty?
得意料理は?
Shrimp chili.
エビチリ
Is it shrimp chili?
エビチリか
Dry person?
辛口派?
Spicy.
辛め
Is it spicy?
辛めか
You can make it like this.
こんな作ってもいい
I'll eat Chinese food in the morning.
朝から中華やったら
That's good.
いいよね
I wonder if it's something I can cook.
料理できるものなのかね
It's not like I'm going to do it right away and drown myself in it, after all.
や っぱすぐやろうと思って溺れるわけじゃないから、
What is cooking?
料理って
surely.
確かに
It takes time.
時間かかるし
If I don't do it, I'll forget.
やらないと忘れるし
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏さんとかはいる?
Would you like to watch the cooking?
料理をご視聴したいとかは?
not at all.
全然
What is that?
それは何?
why?
なんで?
He will make it for you.
作ってくれる
Is your boyfriend good at it too?
彼氏も得意なの?
He will use it.
使ってくれる
nice.
いいね
Why don't you just make Etamania?
エタマニア作ってよとかない?
Not at all.
全然ない
Well, for someone who likes to cook and eat,
じゃあ自分でも料理作るし、食べるの好きな人からして、
How is your boyfriend cooking?
彼氏の料理はどう?
It's delicious.
美味しいです
You're good at it, my boyfriend.
上手なんや、彼氏の
Great, being a man who can cook is a big plus.
いいな、男で料理できるってポイント高いよね
Can't you?
できないですか?
What is it?
なんのですね
As much as I love baking, I live alone.
甘く焼くぐらい、一人暮らしやし
I can handle the fish.
魚は捌けるわ
amazing.
すごい
I can do that, but I can't cook.
それはできるけど料理はできない
Amazing, absolutely amazing.
すごい、全然すごい
why?
なんで?
No cooking.
料理はダメ
I do make tempura and other things, but it's prepared fish.
天ぷらとかはするけどね、捌いた魚
I do eat sashimi, tempura, and fried chicken, but...
刺身とか、天ぷらとか、唐揚げとかはするけど、
I want something rich like simmered.
煮たりとか、ああいう濃ったのは欲しい
Do an episode?
エピソードする?
Yeah.
うん
copper?
どう?
feeling?
気持ち?
Will you be served or not?
ご放肆するか、されるかな?
be done.
される
That's what happened there.
されたんや、そこは
Accident.
意外
I thought maybe I would.
するはかなと思った
But today, I'm not in the mood to indulge.
でも今日はちょっと、俺ご放肆する気分じゃないから
picture?
え?
I'm a flower that I'd like to be known for.
俺はどっちかとされたい花
I see.
なるほど
It makes me feel like a king,
ちょっと王様気分味わいちゃうから、
Will you do your best?
頑張ってくれる?
It's a little hot, so I'm going to bed.
ちょっと暑いし、寝こっか
It's hot.
暑いし
What is string bread?
ひもパンってやつですか?
It's called string bread.
ひもパンってやつ
Eh, it's easy, isn't it?
え、楽なんやっぱそれは?
I feel like it's going to bite me.
食い込みそうなんやけど
It bites in quite a bit though.
結構食い込むけど
This has decreased.
これ分け減ちになった
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's divided and subtracted.
分け減じいで
Is it worth dividing?
分 け減じい?
Neck, not neck, what did I do here?
首で、首じゃない、ここ何やったっけ?
For your neck.
首にとって
picture?
え?
same?
同じ?
What about the soles of your feet?
足の裏は?
I'm usually alone, you know.
普段一人です、その
cute.
可愛い
Toy fan?
おもちゃ派?
Assignment?
指派?
What do you like about toys?
おもちゃやったら何が好き?
Oh, anything.
え、なんでも
anything.
なんでも
I have it at home.
家にあるわ
Can you do your best?
頑張れる?
do my best.
頑張る
You said you want to be treated like that.
されたい派って言ってたけど
Can I have a little lesson?
ちょっとレッスンあっていい?
Yeah.
うん
If you eat too much salt.
ちょっと塩ポン食べ過ぎたら
In the middle of the day, what if I really tried Cresso?
途中、本気でクレッソーやったら何か
I like it at all.
全然好き
Do you like it at all?
全然好き?
It's not about unraveling the strings.
ひも解くんじゃないんや
Ah, do you understand?
あ、解く?
solve?
解く?
Can you solve it?
解ける?
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
My pants got a little dirty.
ちょっとパンツの汚れになった
It seems to be tight.
締まりの良さそうなの
Are you told?
言われる?
Which do you prefer, general or Japan?
一般と日本どっちが好き?
Japan.
日本
Japan and Japan?
日本 と日本か
I've only been drawing the sun.
日なんかばっかり描いてきた
Full month.
月いっぱい
It was tough.
しんどかった
Look here.
こっち見て
Stretch it out in front of you.
前で伸ばして
copper?
どう?
Brat sex.
ガキセックス
Gakise
ガキセ
x.
ック ス
I'm sorry for Kanji.
かんじにごめんなさいよ
Sorry
ごめんな
Sai.
さい
Hold my legs.
足 抱えて
Can I cum inside you?
中 出していい?
中出していい?
Please take it out.
出してくださいよ
Will you clean it up?
綺麗にしてくれる?
gently.
優しく
There's no such thing as upper armpit sex.
ないじゃん、上脇セックス
Have fun.
楽しく
It's an evil eye.
悪目って
You're a little sweaty.
ちょっとね、汗まんでるね
Shall I take a shower?
シャワー浴びよっか
It would be nice if the upper armpits were slippery.
上脇ってすべりゃあっていいよな
it was fun.
楽しかった
It's good to know what not to do.
やってはいけないことっていいよね
That's good.
いいよね
The upper armpits are sticky.
上脇ベタベタ
Sticky.
ベタベタ
It's sticky and disgusting,
ベ タベタとね、気持ち悪いものはね、
Be sticky.
ベタベタして
What did you say?
なんて言った?
So, can you come up?
じゃあ、上がってくれる?
He will come up.
上がってくれる